<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Jesus Ruiz</title><link>https://hesusruiz.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Jesus Ruiz</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 16:25:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hesusruiz.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alastria RedT and GDPR: an analysis</title><link>https://hesusruiz.github.io/posts/redt_gdpr/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 16:25:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hesusruiz.github.io/posts/redt_gdpr/</guid><description>Alastria RedT is a Public-Permissioned blockchain network. I analyse the network from the point of view of GDPR.
Introduction Alastria RedT is a Public-Permissioned blockchain network. I analyse the network from the point of view of GDPR.</description></item><item><title>EU Digital COVID Certificate: lessons for SSI and W3C Verifiable Credentials implementers</title><link>https://hesusruiz.github.io/posts/lessons_eudcc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 20:19:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hesusruiz.github.io/posts/lessons_eudcc/</guid><description>Most Self-Sovereign Identity (SSI) implementations conflate different concepts into one tightly coupled thing. They typically merge together Identification, Verifiable Credentials and a Verifiable Data Repository.
They claim that new identification systems for citizens are required in order to use Verifiable Credentials for solving the problems that citizens have with current identity systems.
In addition, many SSI systems insist on registering the DIDs of the citizens in an immutable public repository (e.</description></item><item><title>Consensus algorithms and blockchain governance</title><link>https://hesusruiz.github.io/posts/second_post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 17:58:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hesusruiz.github.io/posts/second_post/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article analyses the influence of consensus algorithms in the characteristics of governance models of Public-Permissioned blockchain networks, especifically when using Quorum, Besu and Fabric.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>